Reina Graham

Customer Service/ IT Professional

Current location: Auckland, New Zealand (Flexible to relocate)

Phone:

+64211898142

Email:

reinajkgraham@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/reina-graham-461940256/

Skills

- Programming Languages:
- Python (Scikit-learn, Pandas, Matplotlib Keras, NumPy)
- Java
- R
- o MATLAB
- C
- o SQL
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Microsoft Office
- Highly analytical and solve problems in an organised matter
- Technical skills
- Great communication skills
- Able to multitask under pressure with great patience
- Leadership skills
- Very observant with great attention to details

References

Tobias Kingi

Previous Manager at Ramen

Takara

Phone: 022 689 3667

Email:

toby.kingi@hotmail.co.nz

TK Kim

Previous Dispensary Manager at Life Pharmacy St Heliers Phone: 021 023 48535 Email: tkim.pharm@gmail.com

Summary

Highly analytical, organised and detail-oriented recent graduate in Computer and Information Sciences. Great problem solver and a quick learner, easily adapting to any situation with patience. Shown leadership skills and communication skills in a team environment through years of work experience in various sectors.

Experiences

Projects:

Python: Titanic Competition

https://www.kaggle.com/code/reinagraham/titanic-competition

• A data science project to predict the survival rate of Titanic Passengers

Java: Movie Rating App

https://github.com/reijkg2904/MovieRatingApp

Java: Number Guessing Game

https://github.com/reijkg2904/NumberGuessingGameApp

FreeCodeCamp projects

https://www.freecodecamp.org/reijkg2904

Work Experience:

Food and Beverage attendant/Ramen Takara Japanese Noodle and Sake Bar Sep 2022 - Current

- Practised patience and prioritising during busy hours
- High attention to details leading to little to no mistakes.

Pharmacist/Life Pharmacy St Heliers, Locum at various pharmacies Dec 2019 - Sep 2022

- Worked sole-charge as a manager at times took on responsibilities, took initiatives, supported colleagues and educated pharmacy students
- Analytical, problem solving and communication skills improved significantly.

Education

Graduate Diploma in Computer and Information Sciences, GPA 7.5

Auckland University of Technology

Mar 2022 - Nov 2022

Most relevant papers:

- COMP615: Foundation of Data Science, A+
- COMP723: Data Mining and Knowledge Engineering, A+
- COMP503: Programming 2, A
- COMP719: Applied Human Computer Interaction, A

Bachelor of Pharmacy

University of Otago Feb 2015 – Nov 2018

Certificates

FreeCodeCamp

• Responsive Web Design Developer Certification

Kaggle

- Intro to SQL
- Advanced SQL
- Time Series

Currently working towards a **CompTIA A+** certificate.